[
  {
    "question":"Isekai is fantasy in Japanese",
    "answer" : "f",
    "option1" : "n",
    "option2" :"n",
    "option3":"n",
    "option4":"n",
    "isTrueFalse":true
  },
  {
    "question":"King of Skull Servant’s Max Attack is 5000",
    "answer": "f",
    "option1" : "n",
    "option2" :"n",
    "option3":"n",
    "option4":"n",
    "isTrueFalse":true
  },
  {
    "question":"what is the lowest life points you can drop to without losing in yu-gi-oh the card game",
    "answer":"1",
    "option1":"1",
    "option2":"10",
    "option3" : "20",
    "option4": "100",
    "isTrueFalse":false
  },
  {
    "question":"Light is made up of ",
    "answer":"both",
    "option1":"particles",
    "option2" : "rays",
    "option3" : "both" ,
    "option4": "neither",
    "isTrueFalse":false
  },
  {
    "question":"4K resolution is 4 times the resolution of 1080p",
    "answer":"t",
    "option1" : "n",
    "option2" :"n",
    "option3":"n",
    "option4":"n",
    "isTrueFalse":true
  },
  {
    "question":"What percentage of the earth's water is Theoretically consumable" ,
    "answer":"2.5",
    "option1":"2.5",
    "option2":"3",
    "option3":"5",
    "option4": "1.2",
    "isTrueFalse":false
  },
  {
    "question":"How many terabytes in a petabyte?",
    "answer":"1000",
    "option1":"10000",
    "option2":"10000000",
    "option3":"1000",
    "option4": "10",
    "isTrueFalse":false
  },
  {
    "question":"What console saw the release of “The World Ends With You”?",
    "answer":"Nintendo DS",
    "option1":"Nintendo Switch",
    "option2":"Sony Playstation 4",
    "option3":"Nintendo DS",
    "option4": "Sony Playstation 2",
    "isTrueFalse":false
  },
  {
    "question":"How many possible combinations are in a Master lock padlock?",
    "answer":"64000",
    "option1":"10000",
    "option2":"9999",
    "option3" :"64000",
    "option4": "160000",
    "isTrueFalse":false
  },
  {
    "question":"How many rounds can a mp7 with an extended magazine hold?",
    "answer": "40",
    "option1":"10",
    "option2":"20",
    "option3":"30",
    "option4":"40",
    "isTrueFalse":false
  }
]

